Guide to the Roy M. Huffington Oil Company Records, 1977-2006 MS 575
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Addendum, 1981-2008
  - Awards/Honors, 1945-2008
    - Alpha Tau Omega Fraternity member of the Golden circle, 1985-02-10 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - The Alumni Association of Southern Methodist University Distinguished alumni award, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Awards and Honors, 1977-1988 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Awards and honors, 1996-2008 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Grosse Goldene Ehrenzeichen, Grand decoration of honor in gold for services to the republic of Austria, 1997-09-11 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - In grateful recognition of support for the field of aging, Huffington Center on Aging at Baylor College of Medicine, Houston, TX., 1998-04-07 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Southern Methodist University commends for leadership in The Campaign for SMU: A Time to Lead, 2002-06-28 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Certificate of appreciation for invaluable contribution to the initial development of the Indonesian LNG industry, 2002-12-10 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Pohon Buah Nona (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - The Michael T. Halbouty Human Needs award, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Legends medal award presented to Roy M. Huffington by the Texas Alliance of Energy producers (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Medallion presented by Pertamina and the Huffco group in commemoration of the Badak LNG project East Kalimantan, Indonesia dedicated by president Soeharto, 1977-08-01 (Box 28)
    - Badak LNG expansion project NISSHO IWAI Corporation Jakarta, 1981-04 (Box 28)
    - Indonesia Petroleum Association presented to ambassador Roy M. Huffington "Keynote speaker" the 20th annual Indonesia Petroleum association convention Jakarta Indonesia, 1991-10-08 (Box 28)
    - Roy M. Huffington President Office desk name plate (Box 28)
    - In commemoration of the 20th anniversary of the Badak LNG first drop, 1997-07-05 (Box 28)
    - Lighting the Lamp of Excellence Dr. Michael E. Debakey Award, 2002-05-01 (Box 28)
    - Huffington Corporation has sold its wholly owned subsidiary to Elf Aquitaine, Inc. plaque (Box 28)
    - Presented with appreciation to Roy M. Huffington for service as member board of visitors the university cancer foundation (Box 28)
    - Pertamina Huffco Nilam facility Nilam crude oil, 1982-09-14 (Box 29)
    - The University of Texas Health Science center at Houston School of Nursing Center on Aging presents the community advocate award to the honorable Roy M. Huffington for his contributions to improve the quality of life of older persons, 2003 (Box 29)
    - U.S. Postage nursing in appreciation to Phyllis and Roy Huffington partners and UT- Houston school of nursing (Box 29)
    - Crude oil (Box 29)
    - Intereferon Sample (Box 29)
    - Roy M. Huffington and Bankers Trust company a partnership for the future (Box 29)
    - Roy M. Huffington All American Wildcatter statue by John B. Fincher (Box 30)
    - Pertamina Badak LNG plant South Bontang East Kalimantan Indonesia, 1977 (Box 31)
    - Presented to Ambassador Roy M. Huffington for your valued assistance to the Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1990-12-05 (Box 31)
    - Texas Business Hall of Fame presented to Roy M. Huffington, 1992 (Box 31)
    - Houston Producer's Forum Guest speaker, 1993-05-18 (Box 31)
    - All American Wildcatters RMH Belt holder (Box 31)
    - Huffco logo clear block (Box 31)
    - Roy M. Huffington for distinguished Achievement in Management as a Service to the Community, 2001 (Box 31)
    - Badak LNG sales contract (Box 31)
    - Huffco Roy M. Huffington, Inc. and Bankers Trust Company five year fixed rate loan (Box 31)
  - Photographs and films, 1980-1997 (Box 32)
    - Badak LNG project addition plot plan (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Badak LNG plant direct prints (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - LNG Badak photo album, 1997-07-04 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - LNG Badak Photo (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Gas development and export program for Bangladesh (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - George W. Bush Sr. and Roy M. Huffington (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Home (interior), grocery store, and plant (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Huffco engineering exploration and logistics management (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Huffco housing Gunung Bakaran (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Huffco team at track event, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - RMH- hosted events for Indonesians in Houston, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Indonesia restaurant group gathering (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Annual Kerrville gathering of industry leaders (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Offshore drilling rig negatives (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Offshore drilling rig (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Pertamina/Huffco IJV group executive management seminar, 1984-03-27-1984-03-29 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Pertamina/Huffco IJV group executive management seminar, 1984-03-27-1984-03-29 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Photos of presidents, dignitaries, Huffington, and Pertamina office (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Sheikh Ahmed Zaki Y amani and Roy Huffington (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - The Wilheim Schole first cosmopolis award, 1987-02-05 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - A wonderful evening at the Hilton hotel, Vera Kalman was cooking Gulasch, 1992-12-02 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Badak LNG project photo album (Box 32)
    - First LNG shipment Badak LNG sales contract, 1983-08-25 (Box 32)
    - Footage of drilling rig in Galena Park, undated; huff_01 (Box 32a)
      Scope and Contents
      Contains one master mp4, one access mp4, and digitization reports. Video has no sound.
    - Building on Success: The Badak LNG Expansion, Version 1, 1980s; huff_02; Client: film west Singapore Contains one master mp4, one access mp4, and digitization reports. Film is about HuffCo in Indonesia. (Box 32a)
    - Peresmian LNG Bongtang, 1977-08-10; huff_04; Client: Film West Contains one master mp4, one access mp4, and digitization reports. Film has no sound. (Box 32a)
    - Badak LNG-Indonesia's First Gas for Export, Version 1, undated; huff_05 (Box 32a)
      Contains one master mp4, one access mp4, and digitization reports.
    - Badak LNG: Indonesia's First Gas for Export, huff_06 (Box 32a)
    - Building on Success: The Badak LNG Expansion, Version 2, circa 1980s; huff_07 (Box 32b)
    - Badak LNG: Indonesia's First Gas for Export in Spanish, huff_08; print no. 1 Contains one master mp4, one access mp4, and digitization reports. (Box 32b)
    - Syncrude - Independent Valley Energy Company IVEC, huff_10 (Box 32b)
    - Badak LNG: Indonesia's First Gas for Export - shorter version, huff_11 (Box 32b)
  - Oversize, 1985-2006 (Box 33)
    - LNG Badak photo (Box 33)
    - Alpha Tau Omege Fraternity Member of the Golden Circle award, 1985-02-10 (Box 33)
    - The Michael T. Halbouty Human Needs award, 1991 (Box 33)
    - Legends Medal Award presented to Roy M. Huffington by the Texas Alliance of Energy Producers, 2006-09-28 (Box 33)
- Series VI: Roy M. Huffington, Inc. Domestic and Other Interests
  This series is arranged chronologically when possible. Boxes 46 and 47 are additions of related materials from a second round of processing.
  - Southwest Esther: Overriding Royalty File, Vermilion Parish, Louisiana, 1958-1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - December to November Reading Files, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - December to January Reading Files, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Texas Gas Corporation Gas Pipeline, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - December to January Reading Files, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - LaTerre Co. Inc Prospects, 1962-1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - December to January Reading Files, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - April to January Reading Files, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - August to April Reading Files, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - December to August Reading Files, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Working Investments, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Prospero Mangel No. 1, Brooks County, Texas, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Office Memorandums, 1965-1974 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - June to March Reading Files, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - September to July Reading Files, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - December to Septemeber Reading Files, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Suriname Offshore Concession, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Caribbean Shrimp Corporation, 1966-1975 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - A Reserve and Economic Study of Certain Oil and Producing Properties, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Walker No. 1, Hayes Field, Calcasieu Parish, Louisiana, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Virginia International Company, 1968-1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Huffington Sixty-Nine, Limited, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Operating Committee Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Mar Del Plata Shrimp Boat, 1971-1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Huffington Exploration Corporation Drilling Program, 1972-1973 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Operating Committee Minutes, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Receptions and Functions Guest Lists, 1973-1983 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Articles and Addresses, 1974-1977 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Samedan Oil, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting Notes, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Tesoro Oil Division Orders, 1974-1984 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Office Memorandums, 1975-1977 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Financial Forecast, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Lawson Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1975-1980 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Bouillon Pipeline and Facilities, 1976-1980 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Financial Statements, 1976-1980 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors Memorandums, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Career Development Reviews, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Office Procedures Manual, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Huffco Brochures, 1979-1987 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Stock Certificates, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Universe Tankships Inc., 1980 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - June to August Financials, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - September to November Financials, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Promotional Booklet for Abu Dhabi Petroleum Company Ltd, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Huffco Corporate Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Huffco Petroleum Landsmen in Action Photo Slides, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Goals for the 1980s, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Long Term Huffco Plans, 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Long Term Huffco Plans, 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Concession Map of SE Turkey for Huffco Turkey Inc., 1982 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Policy and Procedures Manual, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Gas Marketing, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Huffco Petroleum Corporation Oil and Gas Programs, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Huffco Board Photo Slides, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Ewing Bank and Ship Shoal Status Report, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - First Tranche Petroleum, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Huffco Newsletters, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Sale of Capital Stock to Opicoil America, Inc. Volume 1, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Sale of Capital Stock to Opicoil America, Inc. Volume 2, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Huffco House Party Photographs, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Huffco Brantas, Inc. and Huffco Kahayan, Inc., 1990 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - PetroVietnam and Petechim, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Culver Drilling Prints, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Culver Drilling Company and Stanford Partners, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Partners Tax Projections and Returns, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Partners, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Partners Lease and Partnership Agreements, 1981-1985 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Partners, 1983-1984 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Partners, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Partners, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Partners, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Statement of Facts, Volume 1, 1 of 2, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Statement of Facts, Volume 1, 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Statement of Facts, Volume 2, 1 of 2, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Statement of Facts, Volume 2, 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Upchurch Notes, 1973-1977 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Statement of Facts, Volume 3, 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Statement of Facts, Volume 3, 2 of 2, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Upchurch Part 1, 1965-1980 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Upchurch Part 2, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Upchurch Part 3, 1977-1980 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Upchurch Deposition, 1 of 2, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Upchurch Deposition, 2 of 2, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Upchurch Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Upchurch Documentation and Notes, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - East Java, Indonesia, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Culver Drilling Brochure, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Property Surrender Reports, 1964-1980 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Suggestions for New Ventures, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Huffco Houston Memorandums, 1967-1977 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Employee Titles, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Huffco Turkey, Inc., 1980-1989 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - RMHI Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1 of 2, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - RMHI Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Bully Camp, South Crawley, and Lawson Fields, 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Qatar Northfield Project, 1981-1983 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Organizational Announcements, 1981-1989 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 1983 Houston Budget, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Star Project, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1 of 3, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2 of 3, 1982-1986 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 3 of 3, 1986-1990 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Huffco Turkey, Inc. Visit, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Review of Huffco Operations, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Thrace Gas Project, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Management Meeting, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Briefing Book Summary, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Turkey LNG Import Project, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Nigerian LNG, 1987-1990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cabot Project, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Planning Meeting, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Yemen Research, 1 of 2, 1993-1996 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Yemen Research, 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - International Oil and Gas Establishment Proposal, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Wuntu Field, 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Wuntu Field, 2 of 2, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Yemen Trip, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Petroleum Resource Research Yemen, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Organization Chart, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Huffco Energy Resources Application for Licensing a Foreign Company Branch in Abu Dhabi, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - First Licensing Round-Yemen, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Series VII: Huffco Indonesia and the Indonesian Joint Venture
  This series is arranged chronologically when possible. Box 47 is an addition of related materials from a second round of processing.
  - Indonesian Concession Reading File, 1968-1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Pertamina Product Sharing Contract Correspondence, 1968-1976 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Project K-3, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Badak #1 Geological Well Report, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Pertamina Executive Speeches, 1972-1980 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Applegate Huffco Diary, 1972-1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Book 1 of the Indonesian Venture, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Badak LNG Special Financial Report and Appendix, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Book 4 Financing Agreements, 1 of 2, 1974-1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Book 4 Financing Agreements, 2 of 2, 1974-1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Indonesian Venture Committee and Sub-Committee Notebook, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - PT Badak Natural Gas Liquefaction Limited Company, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Badak LNG Indonesia's First Gas for Export Booklet, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Badak Field Gas Exploration Plan, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Soeharto Correspondence, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Huffco Indonesia Core Mission, circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Book 1 Principle Agreements, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Medical Facilities Available to Employees in Singapore & Indonesia, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Second Annual Medical Evaluation of Facilities in Singapore & Indonesia, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Huffco LNG 7 Handbook, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Badak LNG Report Photo Slides, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Huffco Bontang and Badak Stills, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Future Concerns to Address, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Fourth Annual Medical Evaluation of Facilities in Singapore & Indonesia, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Fifth Annual Medical Evaluation of Facilities in Singapore & Indonesia, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Oil and Operations: Indonesia, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Future Goals and Outlooks, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Huffco Indonesia Correspondence, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Twentieth Anniversary of Huffco Indonesia, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Malaria Memorandum for Huffco Employees, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Huffco Offering Memorandum, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - MIGAS and Huffco Photographs, circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Badak Discovery Field Photographs, circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Meeting Photographs, circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Huffco Indonesia Miscellaneous Photographs, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - LNG Plant Signing Photographs, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Jakarta Huffco Reception Photographs, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Joint Venture Group Meeting Photographs, 1 of 2, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Joint Venture Group Meeting Photographs, 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Daily Operations Photographs, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Indonesian Operations Photographs, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Indonesia in February Photographs, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Badak LNG Completion Dedication Photographs, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Pertamina Sit Down for Badak Expansion Photographs, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Badak Expansion Meeting in Houston, Texas, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Gas Reserves Meeting Photographs, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Huffco Indonesia Stills, circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Houston Gathering Photographs, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Reception for Soeharto Photographs, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Huffco Ladies Luncheon Photographs, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Huffco Indonesia and Pertamina Reception, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - First LNG Shipment Photographs, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Bontang LNG Plant and LNG Gemini Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Equipment and Training at Bontang LNG Plant Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Bontang Planned Community and School Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Banshu Mary and Gemini LNG Ships Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Gas Sampling and Quality Control at Bontang Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Local Kampong and Channel Approach at Bontang Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Hospital Operating Theater at Bontang Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Helicopter Transport at Badak and Bontang & Communications at Bontang Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Workers in Action at Badak Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Gas Plant, Wells, and Pipeline at Badak Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Control Room, Computer Room, and Research Library at Bontang Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Housing Area and Mosque at Bontang Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Kalimantan Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Balikpapan and Santan Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Huffco Indonesia Office Workers Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Thirtieth Anniversary Badak Field Discovery Photographs, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - LNG Plant Workers Classroom Training Photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Indonesian Reference Photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Wijarso Cassette Tape, 1 of 2, undated (Box 39, Item 32)
  - Wijarso Cassette Tape, 2 of 2, undated (Box 39, Item 33)
  - Utomo Cassette Tape, 1 of 2, undated (Box 39, Item 34)
  - Utomo Cassette Tape, 2 of 2, undated (Box 39, Item 35)
  - Indonesia Film, 1 of 2, undated (Box 40, Item 1)
  - Indonesia Film, 2 of 2, undated (Box 40, Item 2)
  - LNG Bontang Dedication Ceremony Film, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Buyers in Jakarta/Bontang for Expansion Meetings Film, 1979 (Box 40, Item 4)
  - Indra Kartasasmita Cassette Tape, undated (Box 40, Item 5)
  - Soedarno Cassette Tape, 1 of 2, undated (Box 40, Item 6)
  - Soedarno Cassette Tape, 2 of 2, undated (Box 40, Item 7)
  - Huffco Pertamina Cassette Tape, undated (Box 40, Item 8)
  - Huffco Indonesia Memorabilia, undated (Box 41)
  - Hotel Indonesia Photo Booklet, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Huffco Indonesia Minutiae, 1975-1985 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Secondary School Sponsorship, 1975-1981 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - East Kalimantan Gas, Indonesia, 1980s (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Stratigraphy and Hydrocarbon Potential of the Klandasan Beds in the Kutei Basin, East Kalimantan, Indonesia, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Pertamina/PSC Training Consortium, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Huffco Indonesia Tour Packet, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Huffco Indonesia Cash Calls, 1981-1983 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Expanded Badak Project, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Train B Reconstruction, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Santan Storage and Crude Oil Liftings Memorandums, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Taiwan Gas Sales, 1984-1987 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Indonesia's Petroleum Sector, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Semberah Oil Development Plan, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Huffco Indonesia Organization Feedback, Summary, and Recommendations, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Pelopor (Pioneer) Award, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Huffco News, 1985-1987 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - LNG-8 Conference and Accompanying Materials, 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - LNG-8 Conference and Accompanying Materials, 2 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Gas Allocation Meeting, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Runtu Block Contracts and Accompanying Materials, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - LNG Badak Report, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary of Indonesian LNG, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Series VIII: Alaska Interstate and Enstar
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Alaska Interstate Proposed Merger, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Interstate (AKI) and Roy M. Huffington, Inc. (RMHI) Stock Negotiation, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - AKI and RMHI, 1978-1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - AKI Proxy Vote Documents, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - AKI Annual Meeting Announcement, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - RMHI and AKI Financials, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - AKI Bulletin, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - AKI Annual Report, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Enstar Corporation Six Months Report, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Enstar Indonesian Investments, 1982-1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - AKI/Enstar Certificates, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Enstar Notes, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Summary of Corporate History of Acquisitions and Divestitures, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Enstar Natural Gas Company Organization Chart, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Enstar Proposed By-law Changes, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Enstar Board of Directors Meeting September 15, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Enstar Board of Directors Meeting November 17, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Stock Updates, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Nine Months Reports, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Enstar Memorandum, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Audit Committee Meeting, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - SEC Enstar Annual Report, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 22)